var questionsObj = {
  quizName : "Demo Quiz II",
  quizTags : ["Demo"],
  startTime : 1540933200000,
  questionCount : 10,
  questions: [
    {
      questionNumber: 'Question 6',
      question: 'Which of these monuments have never been on the 7 wonders of the world list?',
      options: {
        option1: 'Taj Mahal',
        option2: 'Stonehenge',
        option3: 'Hawa Mahal',
        option4: 'The Colosseum'
      },
      correctAnswer: 'Hawa Mahal'
    },
    {
      questionNumber: 'Question 7',
      question: 'What was the first animal to go to the space called?',
      options: {
        option1: 'Ham',
        option2: 'Mickey',
        option3: 'Laika',
        option4: 'Jerry'
      },
      correctAnswer: 'Laika'
    },
    {
      questionNumber: 'Question 8',
      question: 'Who was the first Indian in independent India to have won a medal in an individual Olympic event ?',
      options: {
        option1: 'Dhyan Chand',
        option2: 'Milkha Singh',
        option3: 'K.D Jadhav',
        option4: 'P.T Usha'
      },
      correctAnswer: 'K.D Jadhav'
    },
    {
      questionNumber: 'Question 9',
      question: '"Offside" is a term, most commonly used in which sport',
      options: {
        option1: 'Football',
        option2: 'Chess',
        option3: 'Basketball',
        option4: 'Golf'
      },
      correctAnswer: 'Football'
    },

    {
      questionNumber: 'Question 10',
      question: 'Who said "Democracy is government of the people, by the people and for the people"',
      options: {
        option1: 'Jawahar Lal Nehru',
        option2: 'Abraham Lincoln',
        option3: 'Winston Churchill',
        option4: 'Aristotle'
      },
      correctAnswer: 'Abraham Lincoln'
    },
    {
      questionNumber: 'Question 6',
      question: '15x25/5 = ',
      options: {
        option1: '55',
        option2: '65',
        option3: '75',
        option4: '85'
      },
      correctAnswer: '75'
    },
    {
      questionNumber: 'Question 7',
      question: 'Arrange the following words in alphabetical order : 1.Disclaimer 2. Diagonal 3. Destruction 4. Discount',
      options: {
        option1: '2, 3, 1, 4',
        option2: '3, 4, 1, 2',
        option3: '3, 2, 1, 4',
        option4: '1, 2, 3, 4'
      },
      correctAnswer: '3, 3, 1, 4'
    },
    {
      questionNumber: 'Question 8',
      question: 'Unscramble the following letters to make a dictionary word : LEBASCRB',
      options: {
        option1: 'SCRIBBLE',
        option2: 'SCRABBLE',
        option3: 'SCISSORS',
        option4: 'SCATTERED'
      },
      correctAnswer: 'SCRABBLE'
    },
    {
      questionNumber: 'Question 9',
      question: 'Arrange lowest to highest: A. 15467, B. 1587, C. 15476, D. 1789',
      options: {
        option1: 'B, D, A, C',
        option2: 'D, B, C, A',
        option3: 'C, A, D, B',
        option4: 'A, B, C, D'
      },
      correctAnswer: 'B, D, A, C'
    },
    {
      questionNumber: 'Question 10',
      question: 'If North is to your Right and you take a perpendicular turn towards right, what direction is towards your back?',
      options: {
        option1: 'South',
        option2: 'West',
        option3: 'North',
        option4: 'East'
      },
      correctAnswer: 'South'
    }
  ]}

  module.exports.quizQuestions = questionsObj;